[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "Is the bubble sort algorithm O(n)?",
    "answer": "false"
  },
  { "id": 2, "question": "Are binary trees graphs as well?", "answer": "true" },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "Are binary trees always O(log n)?",
    "answer": "false"
  },
  { "id": 4, "question": "Hash tables are O(1) for lookup?", "answer": "true" },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "A recursive function is a function that calls itself?",
    "answer": "true"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "A binary search starts at the beginning of the collection of items?",
    "answer": "false"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "A pointer whose value is NULL does not point to anything?",
    "answer": "true"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "A balanced binary search tree has the minimum height possible for the tree.",
    "answer": "true"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "A stack is a data structure that follows the FIFO rule?",
    "answer": "false"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "A queue is a data structure that follows the LIFO rule?",
    "answer": "false"
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "Both stacks and queues can have either an array-based or a link-based implementation?",
    "answer": "true"
  }
]
